misskl.com 2016-12-29

# Privacy Policy - Karmaloop.com

* * *

## Information Collection & Use

### Orders

If you purchase a product from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (including name, telephone number, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number and its expiration date).

We use this information for billing purposes and to fulfill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

While making a purchase from karmaloop.com, you are given the option to create a username and password. This user name and password functionality offers our customers the ability to quickly and easily proceed through the check out process on repeat visits. We do not store your credit card information as part of this optional service. There is also the option to receive our email newsletter updates. If you choose to receive these you should expect weekly HTML newsletter content to arrive at the email address you provided with your purchase.

Karmaloop LLC and our subsidiaries are the sole owner of the information collected on karmaloop.com.

### Surveys or Contests

Karmaloop often provides you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address).

We use this information to notify contest winners, award prizes, and to send participants our HTML email newsletter.

We sometimes run contests in conjunction with other websites or services. When we do so, any information you provide as a result of entering the contest or survey may also be provided to the affiliate but such practices will always be clearly marked at the time of entry.

### Tell-A-Friend

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s email address. Your friend will also be subscribed to our weekly HTML email newsletter. Your friend may contact us at <http://www.karmaloop.com/account/unsubscribe> to request that we remove his or her email address from our database.

### Uses of Information

We use the information we collect from you for billing purposes and to fulfill your orders. We do not store your credit card information. If you have created a username and password to the site or if you have signed up to receive our email newsletter updates we may use your purchase history to personalize special offers and promotions for you. These offers and promotions will be delivered to you in the form of an email newsletter.

* * *

## Communications from the Site

### Special Offers and Updates

We will occasionally send you information on products, special deals, and promotions. You can sign up for these emails from us at any time on any page on the site. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications at <http://www.karmaloop.com/account/unsubscribe>.

### Newsletters

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe here: <http://www.karmaloop.com/account/unsubscribe>.

### Customer Service

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.

### Supplementation of Information

In order to process your credit card orders, we use [Verisign](http://www.verisign.com/), a third party service, to validate and verify your account information. All billing and account info is transmitted via https which is a secure encrypted protocol system.

### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website. You cannot opt out of disclosure of your personal information if required by lawful order.

* * *

## Log Files

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. We use two third-party tracking services; [Webtrends](http://www.webtrends.com/) & [Clicktracks](http://www.clicktracks.com/) that use cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors.

* * *

## Third Party Advertisers

The ads appearing on this website are delivered to users by Indiclick, our advertising partner. We do not share any website usage information about users with Indiclick

* * *

## Links to Other Sites

This website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by karmaloop.com. Please be aware that we, karmaloop.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this website.

* * *

## Co-branded sites

Karmaloop occasionally develops co-branded sites so third parties can re-sell our products through their store or website. Co-branded sites are mostly driven by the Karmaloop shopping cart experience and all data collected stays with Karmaloop.

* * *

## Access to Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on our My Account page, or by emailing our Customer Support at [questions@karmaloop.com](mailto:questions@karmaloop.com) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

* * *

## Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We use reasonable technological and physical safeguards to protect personal information you provide to us from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet is 100% secure, however, we make all reasonable efforts to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information. In the unlikely event of a data breach, you will be notified as soon as possible.

If you have any questions about security on our website, you can email us at [questions@karmaloop.com](mailto:questions@karmaloop.com)

* * *

## Use/Access by Third Parties

In addition to the third parties mentioned specifically in this policy, Karmaloop may share your information with third party vendors and affiliates. If Karmaloop shares your personal information with any third party, we will take precautions to ensure that these companies only use your information consistent with this Policy and that reasonable safeguards are taken to ensure the third party provides at least the same level of privacy protection that Karmaloop provides.

* * *

## Business Transitions

In the event karmaloop.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

* * *

## Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

* * *

## Enforcement

Karmaloop will regularly review its policies and practices to determine its continued compliance with the requirements of the Safe Harbor program, PIPEDA and the terms of this privacy policy. Karmaloop designates the European Data Protection Authorities and JAMS to refer unresolved Safe Harbor-related privacy complaints.

* * *

## Safe Harbor / PIPEDA

Karmaloop complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework, satisfying its obligations under the EU Directive on Data Protection, Swiss data protection law, and PIPEDA. Karmaloop has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. Karmaloop’s implementation of these principles are set forth more fully above. To learn more about the U.S. Department of Commerce Safe Harbor program, and to view Karmaloop’s certification, please visit http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/.

Privacy Complaints by European Union Citizens:

In compliance with the Safe Harbor Principles, Karmaloop commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Karmaloop at: 617-695-0117617-695-0117

Customer Service  
Karmaloop  
334 Boylston St, 5th Floor  
Boston, MA 02116  

* * *
